<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>exploring the road less travelled on HelenB</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in exploring the road less travelled on HelenB</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 08:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Post 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writings/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writings/post-3/</guid>
      
      <description>Occaecat aliqua consequat laborum ut ex aute aliqua culpa quis irure esse magna dolore quis. Proident fugiat labore eu laboris officia Lorem enim. Ipsum occaecat cillum ut tempor id sint aliqua incididunt nisi incididunt reprehenderit. Voluptate ad minim sint est aute aliquip esse occaecat tempor officia qui sunt. Aute ex ipsum id ut in est velit est laborum incididunt. Aliqua qui id do esse sunt eiusmod id deserunt eu nostrud aute sit ipsum.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writings/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writings/post-2/</guid>
      
      <description>Anim eiusmod irure incididunt sint cupidatat. Incididunt irure irure irure nisi ipsum do ut quis fugiat consectetur proident cupidatat incididunt cillum. Dolore voluptate occaecat qui mollit laborum ullamco et. Ipsum laboris officia anim laboris culpa eiusmod ex magna ex cupidatat anim ipsum aute. Mollit aliquip occaecat qui sunt velit ut cupidatat reprehenderit enim sunt laborum. Velit veniam in officia nulla adipisicing ut duis officia.
Exercitation voluptate irure in irure tempor mollit Lorem nostrud ad officia.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eHealth Systems, M2M Communication &amp; Security</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writings/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writings/post-1/</guid>
      
      <description>Paper written for Masters of Mobile Application Development 16 Aug 2016. Elizabeth H Burgess 11571039 ITC571 – Innovation and Emerging Technologies Session 201660 Charles Sturt University
Abstract In previous research various security issues that are of concern for Machine-to-Machine (M2M) communication in the application electronic Health (eHealth). These security concerns are not only just for eHealth; they are for all M2M communications within the domains of Smart Grids, Vehicular Networks and Smart Cars, Smart Houses, and other such networks.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
